<JSON_NEW_HELP_ENGLISH>
	<help_txt>
		<choose_title>//nWelcome to Lama Temple 3D scene!
//nThe need novice help
		</choose_title>
		<help1_info>//nManually when roaming, the mouse click the Lama Temple to
//nA surface location will automatically walk to that location.
		</help1_info>
		<over_info>//nVery good!Now you are free to control angle
//nColor to the Lama Temple 3D scene.
		</over_info>
		<start_propmt_text>//nHello!Welcome to Lama Temple. We let
//nFind out more about the functionality of 3D Lama Temple!
		</start_propmt_text>
		<introduce_text>//nTemple introduction
//nClick on the Temple Description "button, I can understand an overview of the Lama Temple, the Lama Temple
//nAnd cultural content, so that a comprehensive understanding of the Lama Temple, and they know
//nKnowledge are related to the actual location within the Lama Temple.
		</introduce_text>
		<take_photos>//nPhotograph
//nJust click the camera button and the beauty you see the Lama Temple, it can be stored in
//nOn their own machines, has been reserved to enjoy.
		</take_photos>
		<system_settings>//nSettings (language switch, music)
//nSystem for foreign tourists set, you can use in the English language
//nThe switch can set the music switches.
		</system_settings>
		<ask_help>//nClick the help button at the bottom of the screen, will you open the full instruction manual, you
//nA comprehensive understanding of all functions and operations of the "3D Lama Temple".
		</ask_help>
		<sand_table>//nElectronic sand table
//nClick on the bottom of the screen "electronic sand table" button, the scene changes to
//nElectronic sand table scene. Functional classification of life, can be intuitive and fast
//nMcNair display Temple facilities, and provide a key to quickly reach the function.
		</sand_table>
		<wander_route>//nRoaming routes
//nClick on the "roaming line button interface on the right, select the appropriate
//nRoaming path. "Roaming" in the air overlooking the way
//nCan head way in the ground, the Lama Temple, the internal building structure
//nAnd Yonghegong views panoramic view.
		</wander_route>
	</help_txt>
</JSON_NEW_HELP_ENGLISH>